cloudopt.net 2019-12-29

# 

Thank you for using Cloudopt and for your support and trust. We are committed to
protecting your privacy information and ensuring your control over your own
information. This Privacy Agreement is designed to help you understand what
information we collect and why. You will agree to this Agreement by default when
you use our product or service.
(I) What information we collect
     1. To create an account or to receive certain notifications, you may need to
     provide us your personal information, including your email, mobile number,
     etc., or the authorization, nickname, gender of your social network account,
     etc. Even if you are not logged in, you can choose to provide us with relevant
     information (e.g., an e-mail address to receive updates).
     2. Information created or uploaded while you are using Cloudopt’s websites,
     apps, mini programs and other products.
     3. If you grant the right, we might fetch some information through your social
     account, such as unique ID, nickname ( of Wechat for example ).
     4. For better service, we might also collect information about your app, your
     browser, and your device, to provide useful features, such as software auto
     update, or auto language adaptation. The information we collect includes
     unique ID, browser type and configuration, device type and configuration,
     operation system and application versions. We might also collect IP addresses,
     crash reports, system activities, and related times and origin reference URLs.
     For your security, we collect this information anonymously and do not
     associate user identities with it.
     5. When a Cloudopt application needs to collect information other than
     mentioned above, we will require your permission through obvious prompts or
     popup windows, as well indicate the purpose of the permission when
     request. When you grant or open the permission, you authorize us to collect
     and use this personal information. After you revoke or close the permission, we
     will stop collecting and using you information, but we don’t promise that the

      services will continue to be available. We will also ensure that your
      authorization is sought only in lawful circumstances and uses.
      6. We will use browser cache, cookies and other features to ensure that you
      can enjoy the best experience while browsing our website. Browsing our
      website means you have no objection about using cache. You can change your
      cache settings at any time.
(II) Why we collect the information
      1. We will use the information to provide some of Cloudopt’s services, such as
      Cloud Synchronization.
      2. We will use the information to ensure that your use of the services is normal,
      for example, we use it for tracking interruptions or troubleshooting problems
      you reported to us.
      3. We will use the data to analyze and evaluate the usage of Cloudopt services.
      4. We will use your information to protect your account security. For example, a
      login needs to be verified through the email you provide.
      5. To inform you of changes to our products, services or terms.
(III) About Cookies and Third Parties
We will use cookies to distinguish you from other users of this site, and we will use
tools such as Google Statistics to analyze site visits. If you want to learn more about
this, you can visit the website of the third party tools we use to see their privacy
agreement. Please note that these service providers have their own privacy policies,
and we do not accept any responsibility for these policies. Please confirm their
privacy policy before submitting any personal information on these sites.
(IV) When do we share your information with certain Third Parties

     1. Under circumstances that are related to national security, national defence
     security, public security, criminal investigation, etc.
     2. Under circumstances of detecting, preventing, resolving problems of fraud,
     security, technology.
     3. After some agreements or contacts was signed based on your request.
     4. Under other circumstances, such as when using email dynamic verification
     code login, we would share the information only with your authorization and
     consent. .
(V) How we protect your privacy
     1. We transmit data through high intensity HTTPS encryption.
     2. We will use WAF and other tools to protect websites, servers and databases.
     3. For your password and other extremely important data, we will strictly
     encrypt.
     4. In the event of a security incident such as a personal information disclosure,
     we will launch the contingency plans to prevent the security incident from
     expanding and notify you by email and other ways.
(VI) Regional differences
The servers we use to process your data may not be located in your country. Data
protection laws vary by country, and their strength of data protection also varies.
The way we manage data is based on the local laws.
(VII) Feedback and suggestions
If you have any problem with the way we manage you personal data, please send it
by email to support@cloudopt.net .

(VIII) Updates of the policy
We will update this policy from time to time. This may be to reflect the changes in
the products or services we provide, or changes in our internal process methods, or
to reflect changes in the laws.
The simplest way to confirm an update is to view the latest version of this policy on
this site.
Each time we update the policy, we update the policy version number and the
effective date which are shown at the end of the policy. If you continue to use our
services, you accept the amended policy.
This policy does not apply to services provided by other companies or individuals.
All rights to interpret and modify this policy are owned by Cloudopt.
This is policy version 2019-01, which came into effect on 20.01.2019.
